<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Reels - Interview Questions</title>
    <description>Daily AI-generated technical interview questions for system design, algorithms, frontend, backend, DevOps, and more.</description>
    <link>https://reel-interview.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="https://reel-interview.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:10:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <url>https://reel-interview.github.io/favicon.svg</url>
      <title>Code Reels</title>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 New Questions Added</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily AI-powered question generation added 1 new questions across 1 channels.

Sample questions:
• What is the difference between XSS and CSRF attacks?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-17-added</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>security</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 New Questions Added</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily AI-powered question generation added 1 new questions across 4 channels.

Sample questions:
• Explain the event sourcing pattern and its key benefits in distributed systems?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-16-added</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>backend</category>
      <category>database</category>
      <category>devops</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 New Questions Added</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily AI-powered question generation added 16 new questions across 19 channels.

Sample questions:
• How would you design a message queue system that guarantees exactly-once delivery while maintaining high throughput for real-time event processing?
• What&apos;s the difference between REST, GraphQL, and gRPC in terms of protocol and data format?
• How would you optimize a time-series analytics query that scans 100M+ rows across multiple date partitions when the WHERE clause cannot be pruned effectively?
• What is the primary difference between Ansible, Puppet, and Chef in configuration management?
• Your microservice has a 99.9% availability SLO over 30 days with a 1-hour burn rate alert threshold. If you experience a 10-minute outage at 10% traffic impact followed by a 5-minute outage at 100% traffic impact, what&apos;s your remaining error budget and should you trigger the burn rate alert?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-16-added</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>algorithms</category>
      <category>backend</category>
      <category>database</category>
      <category>devops</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 New Questions Added</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily AI-powered question generation added 25 new questions across 26 channels.

Sample questions:
• How does Raft consensus algorithm ensure leader election and log replication in distributed systems?
• How would you implement a React useMemo hook to optimize a recursive Fibonacci function with memoization, and what are the key trade-offs between top-down memoization vs bottom-up tabulation in this context?
• What is a closure in JavaScript and how does it enable data encapsulation?
• How would you implement JWT authentication with RS256 signing and refresh token rotation to prevent token replay attacks?
• How does MongoDB&apos;s document structure differ from SQL&apos;s table rows for storing user data?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-15-added</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>algorithms</category>
      <category>frontend</category>
      <category>backend</category>
      <category>devops</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 Questions Improved</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AI-powered improvement bot enhanced 18 questions with better explanations and diagrams.

Sample questions:
• How do Incident Response Playbooks automate security incident workflows using predefined procedures and role-based actions?
• How do different load balancing algorithms distribute traffic across servers, and what are the trade-offs between performance and resource utilization?
• How does React&apos;s Virtual DOM diffing algorithm work during reconciliation, and what role do keys play in optimizing list updates?
• How do cloud migration tools automate application and data transfer between on-premise and cloud environments?
• How does a Service Catalog enable self-service infrastructure provisioning in an Internal Developer Platform?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-15-improved</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>backend</category>
      <category>sre</category>
      <category>algorithms</category>
      <category>networking</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 New Questions Added</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily AI-powered question generation added 25 new questions across 25 channels.

Sample questions:
• How would you design a multi-tier caching strategy with cache warming, invalidation, and fallback for a 99.9% availability e-commerce platform?
• Given a directed weighted graph with up to 10^6 edges and frequent edge weight updates, design a data structure that supports dynamic shortest path queries with sub-millisecond response time?
• How would you implement a custom useDebounce hook that works with React&apos;s concurrent features and prevents stale closures?
• How would you implement eventual consistency in a multi-region DynamoDB application with write conflicts?
• How would you design a GitOps multi-cluster deployment strategy using ArgoCD that handles blue-green deployments with zero-downtime rollback across 50+ clusters while maintaining state consistency?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-15-added</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>algorithms</category>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>frontend</category>
      <category>database</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27 New Questions Added</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily AI-powered question generation added 27 new questions across 27 channels.

Sample questions:
• How would you implement session affinity (sticky sessions) in HAProxy while maintaining high availability, and what are the trade-offs compared to stateless load balancing?
• How would you implement a thread-safe LRU cache using a HashMap and DoublyLinkedList, considering eviction policy and O(1) operations?
• How would you implement a performance budget system that automatically detects bundle regressions and enforces lazy-loading boundaries in a large-scale React application?
• How does the Saga pattern handle distributed transactions across multiple microservices?
• What is the difference between READ COMMITTED and REPEATABLE READ isolation levels in database transactions?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-14-added</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>sre</category>
      <category>backend</category>
      <category>algorithms</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Reels Launch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Initial release with 185+ questions across 20 channels]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2024-12-14-initial</guid>
      <link>https://reel-interview.github.io/whats-new</link>
      <category>system-design</category>
      <category>algorithms</category>
      <category>frontend</category>
      <category>backend</category>
      <category>database</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>